《烈探雷彻》前情提要
Previously on Reacher...
我收到你的消息了
I got your message.
110特别调查组 “10-30” 这是求救信号
110th, 10-30. A distress call.
卡尔文弗朗茨被谋杀了
Calvin Franz was murdered.
如果他给你打过电话 那他可能也给队里其他人打过
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
我给奥唐纳 迪克森 桑切斯 和奥罗斯科打了电话 都没人接
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco. No one's answering.
我买通了门房
I paid off the concierge.
他指认内格利登记入住
He I.D.'d Neagley as checking in.
盯紧那家酒店还有他们
Just keep an eye on that hotel and them.
-没人会知道你是谁 -但你知道
No one will really know who you are. But you know.
-嘿 奥唐纳 -嘿 内格利
Hey, O'Donnell. Hey, Neagley.
只是一个名单 所有名字的首字母都是AM
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials "A.M."
我刚得到的是一页又一页的随机数据
I just got page after page of random numbers.
-没有顺序 没有意义 什么都没 -至少我们觉得没有 而且暂时而已
No order, no meaning. Nothing. At least to us, for now.
你有什么想法
What are you thinking?
我觉得有人一心想干掉特别调查员
I'm thinking there's someone hell-bent on taking out the special investigators.
他们是冲我们来的
And they're coming after us.
很好
Good.
如果他们的目标是110小组 那他们怎么还没杀我们
So, if someone's coming after the 110, how come they haven't made a run at the three of us yet?
你之前跟家人在树林里 没人能找到我
You were in the woods with your family, no one can ever find me
或许还没轮到内格利
and maybe they just hadn't gotten around to Neagley yet.
他们去了我们的酒店房间
They were in our hotel rooms,
也许他们是想抓或者杀了我们 随后因故不得不匆忙离开
maybe to grab us or take us out, but then had to bail for some reason.
我们得再试着警告其他人
We need to try again to warn the others.
-我会给桑切斯和奥罗斯科打电话 -我来联系迪克森
I'll call Sanchez and Orozco. I got Dixon.
街对面几栋房子外有一辆黑色轿车
There's a black sedan across the street, couple houses down.
跟昨天遇到的是同一辆
Same one as yesterday.
我猜你说得对 我们被跟踪了
Guess you were right. We're being followed.
你打算怎么处理
How you want to play this?
我要去做个自我介绍
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
看看这个该死的美男子
Look at this fucking beaut.
他打算干什么呢
What's he think he's gonna do?
我他妈的鼻子 兄弟
Fucking nose, man.
有枪
Gun!
就像过去美好的时光
Just like the good old days.
是啊 你在一旁观望 而我把所有工作都做完了
Yeah, you on the sidelines while I do all the work.
伙计们 这是他的枪
Uh, fellas, this was his gun.
纽约市警察局
NYPD?
名叫盖塔诺拉索
Name's Gaitano Russo.
嘿 别看我 你把所有工作都做完了
Don't look at me. You did all the work.
我得说 兄弟 你闯大祸了
Got to say, man. Major screwup.
拉索一醒来 整个纽约市警察局都会追捕你
Soon as Russo wakes up, the entire NYPD's gonna be after your ass.
你为什么下手那么狠
Why'd you got to hit him so hard, huh?
我出手从不手软
I don't hit soft.
-袭警可是要坐很久的牢 -那只狗的事情让我很生气
Well, a cop puncher's gonna do some serious time. I was pissed about the dog,
我以为他参与了杀害弗朗茨和斯旺
and I assumed he was involved in killing Franzy and Swan.
你怎么教我们的 “在调查中 假设害死人”
What did you teach us? "In an investigation, assumptions kill."
是“在调查时 细节至关重要”
No, it was "In an investigation, details matter".
我没杀他 只是打断了他的鼻子 他醒来时会没事的
I didn't kill him, just broke his nose. He'll be fine when he wakes up.
糟了 盖塔诺拉索
Shit. Gaitano Russo.
又叫盖伊拉索 他是弗朗茨谋杀案的调查人员
Guy Russo. He's the investigating officer in Franz's homicide.
-我在档案中看到过他的名字 -他是怎么开始跟踪你的
I saw it in the files. And how'd he get on your tail?
纽约市警察局看到弗朗茨 给你打了电话 标记了你的名字
NYPD saw the calls Franz made to you, flagged your name,
你买票的时候 他们收到了提醒
got an alert when you bought the plane tickets,
自从你落地以后一直跟着你 问题是 为什么
been on you since you landed. Question is "why?"
问题是 哪里
Question is "where?"
哪里可以藏一个近两米的重罪犯 这样你就不会被关进监狱了
As in, where do we hide a six-foot-five felon so you don't wind up in the pokey.
我不走 这里是案发现场
I'm not leaving. The case is here.
也许不是
Maybe not.
我给桑切斯和奥罗斯科的办公室 打电话时 语音信箱已经满了
When I called Sanchez and Orozco's office, voice mail was full.
这是个噩兆
That's a bad sign.
考虑到这位“拳王” 击倒了一位执法人员
So it might not be a bad time to get out of Dodge,
现在出去避风头或许不失为好主意
considering Cocky Balboa here just knocked out a lawman.
好吧 我们去大西洋城
Fine. We'll head down to Atlantic City,
看我们能不能找到那些人
see if we can find the guys.
首先 我们要退房 并在拉索恢复知觉
First we got to check out of our hotel and find a more generic ride
让警方“小心提防”你之前 找到更普通的交通工具
before Russo regains consciousness and puts out a BOLO.
路虎揽胜太显眼了
Range Rover's too conspicuous.
就是因为你 我们才不能用好东西
You're the reason we can't have nice things.
烈探雷彻
第二季第二集
等等 我不明白 是出车祸了吗
Wait, I don't understand. Was it a car accident?
没有 他就踹了一下车
No, he just kicked the car.
好吧 那为什么 安全气囊都弹出来了
Well, then how the hell did the airbag go off?
他踹了一下车
He kicked the car,
然后把警察拉了出来 狠狠地揍了一顿
then he pulled the cop out and he knocked his dick in the dirt.
这家伙就是头野兽
I'm telling you, this guy's a beast.
到时候 我需要支援
When the time comes, I'm gonna need some backup.
会给你安排支援的
And you'll get it.
但现在 你继续跟踪监视他们 别搞砸了
But for now, you just stay on their asses, and don't fuck this up.
明白
Understood.
机场临时停车仅在一号停车场
Short-term airport parking only in Lot 1.
特里蒙特有辆2019款雅阁 正在出售 价格低于市场价
There's a 2019 Accord for sale up in Tremont for way under market value.
仅限现金交易
Cash-only deal.
布朗克斯区最常被盗的车型之一 他不想要任何文件吗
One of the most stolen makes and models for sale in the Bronx, and the guy wants no paperwork?
我们坐进去 就跟火烧屁股一样
We sit in that thing, we burn our asses.
我们别无选择 我们被警方标记了 什么都租不了
We don't have a choice. We're flagged in the system. We can't rent anything under our names.
我们开着偷来的车到处走 那很有可能被逮捕
Well, we drive around in a stolen vehicle, we risk getting pinched.
我有解决办法了
I've got our solution.
你的卧底工作怎么样了
How was your undercover job?
雷彻
Reacher.
你怎么知道我在卧底
How'd you know I was undercover?
考虑到当时的情况 你会马上过来
Considering the circumstances, you would've come right away.
但你没有 这意味着 你最近才收到我们的消息
But you didn't, which can only mean you didn't get our messages until recently.
如果你在休假 你会向你的办公室汇报
But if you were on vacation, you would've checked in with your office periodically.
所以你一定是去做卧底了 还藏得很深
So you had to be working undercover, deep undercover,
没办法频繁签到
where frequent check-ins aren't always possible.
你还是一如既往地厉害啊
Same old Reacher.
我在调查一起企业贪污案
Corporate embezzlement case.
在德克萨斯州待了很久
Stuck in Texas so long, I started to think
久到我都开始觉得自己 喜欢牛仔靴和高中橄榄球了
I actually liked cowboy boots and high school football.
你还带着假身份证吗
Still got your fake ID with you?
-带着呢 -很好
-Yeah. -Good.
-拿它去租车吧 -为什么要保密
Use it to rent the car. What's with all the secrecy?
内格利 奥唐纳和我被警方标记了
Neagley, O'Donnell and I have been flagged in the system.
我还打晕了一名警察
And I punched out a cop.
好吧 并不意外
Of course you did.
那么
So...
弗朗茨
Franz.
是的
Yeah.
斯旺也凶多吉少
And Swan, most likely.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科也失踪了
Sanchez and Orozco are MIA, too.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 那我们来调查吧
Okay, so we take care of business.
不要惹特别调查员
You do not mess with the special investigators.
接下来
Next.
-一定要租一辆 -SUV 我知道 你需要车内空间高点
Make sure you get an... SUV. I know. You need the headroom.
太好了 很高兴看到你还在这里
Good. Glad to see you're still here.
感觉我永远都不会离开
Feel like I'm never gonna leave.
如果世界上任何一个 军事基地报告了任何违规行为
If it's reported at any Army base anywhere in the world,
无论多么轻微 我们都得处理
no matter how minor the infraction, we're copied on it.
你发现什么特别的事了吗
Well, anything jump out at you?
是的 20分钟前 有一只蜜露大小的老鼠
Yeah, a rat the size of a honeydew about 20 minutes ago.
说真的
-Seriously? -Yeah.
它又回到那堆箱子那边了
It's back in those boxes somewhere.
好恶心
Gross.
说到老鼠 我觉得 我发现了一只可疑的“老鼠”
Well, speaking of rats, I think I smell one.
阿富汗的一名指挥官 认为有人在偷航空燃料
A commanding officer at a base in Afghanistan thinks someone's stealing aviation fuel.
把汽油抽走 然后再卖出去
Siphoning off gas to resell it on the side?
这不是军方想让我们优先处理的案子
Not exactly the kind of priority case the Army wants us taking on.
我觉得并不是有人在偷取并倒卖燃料
Right, but see, I don't think anybody's stealing and reselling anything.
看看这些数字 它们总能说明问题
Take a look at these numbers. They always tell a story.
我注意到每次基地里有燃料丢失时
See, I noticed that every time fuel went missing from the base,
都是在一趟特定的航班之后
it was always after a specific flight.
即每当C-17 将悍马车运回美国的时候
Whenever C-17s ferried Humvees back home to the States.
我的意思是 这是个小细节 但在调查时 细节至关重要
I mean, it's a minor detail, but in an investigation, details matter.
我喜欢这句
I like that.
我会说这句的
I'm gonna use it.
我的就是你的
What's mine is yours.
那么
So...
你推测出来了吗
you have a theory?
是的 没有迹象表明基地附近
Yeah. There's been no indication of black market fuel sales
存在黑市燃料销售的情况
anywhere on or around the base,
那这些燃料是怎么消失的呢
so how does all that fuel go missing?
让燃料消失的最佳方式 就是把它烧了
Best way to make gas disappear is to burn it up.
没错 内格利有储藏运输石油的经验
Exactly. Now, Neagley's got the bulk fuel experience
她认为所有运送悍马的航班 都是故意过度加油的
and she thinks all the Humvee flights are intentionally being over-fueled.
但当这些飞机降落时
But, when those planes land,
油箱中的燃油量与预期相符
the amount of fuel in the tanks is exactly what's expected,
这些都被记录到账簿中了
and that gets logged into the books.
怎么会这样
So, how does that happen?
多余的燃料是在飞机运输不为人知的
The excess fuel is being used to transport more weight
-额外货物的过程中消耗掉的 -对
than people realize is on the plane. Yeah.
运输了一些沉重而秘密的东西
Something heavy and secret is being moved.
没错 悍马车里有违禁品
Exactly. Contraband in the Humvees.
毒品 枪支 被盗现金 上述所有
Drugs, guns, stolen cash, all of the above.
干得好 迪克森
Good work, Dixon.
你找到了一起值得我们关注的案子
You just found a case worthy of our attention.
我不知道你的感觉 但这些调查让我口干舌燥
I don't know about you, but all this sleuthing's made me thirsty.
想去庆祝一下吗
Want to go celebrate?
你可以请我喝一杯
You can buy me a drink.
我得继续处理这些报告
I got to keep working on these reports.
-下次吧 -好的
Maybe next time. Yeah.
但再说一次
But again,
-干得好 迪克森 -是啊
excellent work, Dixon. Yeah.
没问题 如我所说 数字总能说明问题
No problem. Like I said, numbers always tell the story.
这些数字跟你说明问题了吗
So, the numbers telling you a story?
是的 但这就像晦涩难懂的电影 完全无法理解
Yeah, and it's a David Lynch film. It's totally incomprehensible.
如果这些是分数 那写下这些数字的人就太粗心了
I mean, if these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
有些没被约分
Some of them aren't even reduced.
我也注意到了这一点
I noticed that, too.
也许这些数据代表数量
Maybe the numbers represent hard quantities.
比如 十分之八的某物 而不是五分之四的某物
Like, eight out of ten somethings, and not just four-fifths of something?
有可能
Maybe.
嗯 有可能 除此以外 还有两件事很突出
Yeah, maybe. Beyond that, two things stick out.
这里面没有百分之百 也就是说没有九分之九
None of these are 100%, meaning there's no nine out of nine
或十分之十 前四页有26个数字
or ten out of ten, and the first four pages have 26 numbers,
第五页有27个 最后两页又是26个
the fifth has 27 and the last two have 26 again.
可能是巧合 只是信息的罗列方式
Could be an accident. Just the way the information's spaced.
看起来是刻意而为之的 每一页都不满
No, seems deliberate to me. None of these pages are full.
那一连串AM开头的名字呢
What about the list of A.M. names?
没有任何意义 我同意你们的看法 应该是化名
Means nothing to me. I agree with you guys. It's got to be an alias.
也许是对110小组怀恨在心的人
Maybe it's someone with a grudge against the 110th?
我们逮捕了很多人
We've arrested a lot of people.
詹姆斯巴尔呢
What about James Barr?
他技术高明 有神经质
I mean, that guy's got the skills and a screw loose.
巴尔是名射手 无法想象 他把人从直升机上扔下去的画面
Barr's a shooter. Can't picture him throwing someone out of a helicopter.
我去年在印第安纳州遇见了他
Plus, I ran into him in Indiana last year.
他现在欠我人情
He owes me now.
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
“松林荒原”
Pine Barrens.
大约有一百万英亩
About a million lonely acres.
很像他们在纽约北部 发现弗朗茨尸体的地方
A lot like the spot Upstate New York where they found Franz.
他们把他破碎的尸体扔在那里 任其腐烂
They left his broken body out there to rot.
据我们所知 斯旺也在那里
For all we know, Swan's out there, too.
还有桑切斯和奥罗斯科
And Sanchez. And Orozco.
没有布鲁斯电台吗
There's no blues station?
兄弟 我们现在在泽西
Bro, we're in Jersey.
是我手机上的
It's from my phone.
以前你不在的时候 弗朗茨总是在总部大声放这首歌
Franz used to blast this at HQ all the time when you weren't around.
放着吧
Leave it.
他们用假名字租了一辆车 但是是卡拉迪克森去租的
They rented a car under a fake name, but it's, uh, it's Karla Dixon.
她现在跟他们汇合了
She's with them now.
他们前往大西洋城 可能是去找他们的伙伴
They're headed towards Atlantic City, probably gonna try to find their missing buddies.
很好 一个地方 一网打尽
Good. All in the same place at once.
你到大西洋城以后 杀了他们
When you get there, take them out.
收到
Copy that.
你还记得我说过我需要支援吗 我认识一些当地的人才
You remember what I said about needing backup? I know some local talent.
你需要谁 尽管带上
Well, bring in whoever you need.
我们会付钱
We'll cover the tab.
我只希望你明天干掉他们
I just want them dead by tomorrow.
听见了吗 让他们死翘翘
You hear me? Fucking dead.
新泽西州大西洋城
就像弗朗茨的办公室一样
Just like Franz's office.
还像我们的酒店房间
And our hotel rooms.
你说过他们洗劫了斯旺的住处
You said they hadn't trashed Swan's place.
-是的 -把那加入事物列表
Yup. Add that to the list of things
一定意味着什么
that must mean something.
你们知道奥罗斯科 会不带打火机出门吗
You guys ever know Orozco to go anywhere without his lighter?
美好时光
Better days.
只有我一个人没有这张照片吗
Am I the only one of us that doesn't have this photo?
-我有 -我有
-Got mine. -Got mine.
我的放在书架上
On my bookshelf.
家里没有墙的话 很难把它挂墙上
Hard to hang a picture on your wall when you don't have walls.
我们在这里是浪费时间
We're wasting our time here.
我同意 我们有凶手想要的东西 所有值得找的东西
Agreed. We have what the killers want, and anything worth finding,
他们已经得手了
they already got.
接下来去哪儿
Where to next?
去一家酒吧
A bar.
看看桑切斯和这个女人的这些照片
Look at these photos of Sanchez and this woman.
-五十岁以下的人谁还会裱照片啊 -我们会
Who under 50 frames photos? We do.
除了110小组那张 你还有多少照片
Other than the 110th, how many photos you have at your house?
-不多 -但她的加了相框 所以她很重要
Not many. But she's framed, so she's important.
我们要去幸运酒吧
We're going to the Lucky Lounge.
幸运酒吧
不 你们俩待在这里
No. You two stay here.
你们俩看起来像警察
You both look like cops.
你们俩又像什么
What do you two look like?
《小姐与流浪汉》
Lady and the Tramp.
嘿 这个女人今天上班吗
Hey. This woman working today?
你是谁
Who are you?
豪尔赫桑切斯的朋友
Friends of Jorge Sanchez.
嘿 杜尔斯
Hey, Dulls.
这俩说他们是桑切斯的朋友 想跟米莱娜谈谈
These guys say they're friends of Sanchez, want to talk to Milena.
带他们去后面 她在记账
Take them back to the office. She's doing the books.
米莱娜
Milena.
拿着你的东西 立刻离开这里
Take your shit and get out of here, now.
我知道他不一样
I get that he's a different kind of guy,
但我们的指挥官居然买二手内衣
but our commanding officer buys used underwear.
-那不是照片里的女孩吗 -妈的
Isn't that the girl from the photo? Oh, shit.
嘿
Hey!
我们就只能走到这里了
This is as far as we're going.
怎么回事 伙计们
What's going on, fellas?
别再来搞我们的朋友了
You guys are gonna stop coming around here and messing with our friends.
听我说 朋友 你有点
Look, pal, you somehow got...
别碰我
Don't touch me!
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
走啊
Move your ass.
别再打了 我受够了
I'm done, I'm done.
还好奥唐纳和我没进去
Well, it's a good thing O'Donnell and I didn't go in.
否则可能会出岔子
Something could've gone wrong.
你在交朋友吗 大块头
You making friends, big fella?
抱歉 如果我知道你们是谁 就不会逃跑了
I'm so sorry. I never would've run if I'd known who you were.
我应该认出你们的 我在豪尔赫的照片里看到过你们
I should've recognized you from Jorge's photos.
我的朋友们只是想保护我
My guys were just looking out for me.
大约一周前 一个可怕的家伙 来这里问过她
Scary dude came in here asking for her about a week ago.
那家伙说他和桑切斯以及奥罗斯科 一起在做某个大型安全工作
Said he was working with Sanchez and Orozco on some big security job.
是个宽肩秃顶的家伙
Broad-shouldered bald guy?
不是 他有头发
No. He had hair.
脸颊上有伤疤
Scar down his cheek.
他想知道桑切斯有没有 留给我任何数字存储设备
He wanted to know if Sanchez had left any kind of digital storage device with me.
我不知道他在说什么
I-I had no idea what he was talking about.
那家伙给我一种不祥的感觉 他一走 我就给豪尔赫打了电话
I got a bad vibe off the guy, so soon as he left, I called Jorge.
他没接
He didn't answer.
他们之前也因为工作失联过 但这次
They've gone dark before, part of the job, but this...
感觉不一样
feels different.
你说你认识桑切斯
Then you come in, claiming to know Sanchez,
而你看起来像是被雇来的打手
looking like the kind of people somebody'd hire to rough someone up.
无意冒犯 我以为你不可信
No offense. Assumed you were bad news.
你知道桑切斯和奥罗斯科有没有跟
Do you know if Sanchez and Orozco had any recent contact
卡尔文弗朗茨或托尼斯旺联系吗
with Calvin Franz or Tony Swan?
他几周前来过 他们已经很久没见面了
Actually, yeah. He was here a couple weeks ago. They hadn't seen each other in forever.
我给他们拍了张照
I took a picture of them.
他们当时在调查一起案子
They were working a case together.
-桑切斯跟你说的 -是的
Sanchez told you that? Yeah.
什么案子
What was it?
他没提细节
He didn't mention details.
斯旺也参与了吗
Was Swan involved?
他没来大西洋城
He didn't come down to A.C.,
但我听到他们提到了他的名字
but I heard them mention his name.
你们问过弗朗茨这件事吗
You tried asking Franz about this?
-我们问不了 -为什么
-We can't. -Why not?
有人把他从直升机上扔了下去
Someone threw him out of a helicopter.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你们觉得豪尔赫 和曼努埃尔也死了吗
You think Jorge and Manuel are dead, too?
我们还不知道
We don't know yet.
如果他们还活着 我们会找到他们 但我们需要你帮忙
If they're alive, we'll find them, but we need your help.
你还记得什么没告诉我们的事情吗
Is there anything else you can recall that you haven't told us?
我不知道
I don't know.
我上次看见豪尔赫时 他坐在那边那张凳子上
Last time I saw Jorge, he was sitting on that stool right there.
他接了一个电话 似乎很重要
He got a call. Seemed important.
他说什么了
He say anything?
他重复了几个数字 好像因此很惊讶
Kind of. He-he repeated a couple of numbers, kind of like he was surprised by them,
或者担心
or-or worried, maybe.
他说他要出去 然后就再也没回来
Then he said he was going out for a while, and he never came back.
-你记得那些数字吗 -记得
Do you remember the numbers? Yeah.
他说
He said,
“六千五 每手十万” 不知道是什么意思
"650 at 100k each." No idea what he meant by that.
-你确定 -非常确定
You're sure that's what he said? I'm positive.
他说:“六千五 每手十万”
He said, "650 at 100k,"
他吻了我的脸颊 跑出了那扇门
he kissed me on the cheek and he ran out that door.
你会记得你爱的人 对你说的最后一句话
You remember the last words someone you love said to you.
我们已经掌握了数字 有纽约车牌
We've got the numbers, we've got the New York plates.
也许这事与痛恨110小组的人无关
Maybe this isn't about someone with a grudge against the 110th.
我们中的四人很可能已经被杀害了
If you haven't noticed, it's pretty likely four of us have already been killed already.
米莱娜说弗朗茨几周前来过这里
Milena said Franz was here a couple weeks ago.
如果某些事让他们觉得 我们处于危险之中
If the guys were onto something that made them think we were all in danger,
那他们当时就会给我们打电话 而不是几周后才打
they would've called then, not weeks later.
六千五 每手十万 我们说的是六千五百万美元
650 at 100k, we're talking 65 million bucks.
黑筹码太多了
That's a lot of black chips.
大多数地方 不是这里
Most places. Not here.
大西洋城的赌场大量敛财 怎么
Atlantic City casinos rake in, what?
赌场的年总收入应该是几十亿
Gross gaming revenue's got to be a couple billion a year, easy.
六千五百万 如果随着时间的推移
65 million, if taken carefully, over time,
可能会被忽视一段时间
could go unnoticed for a while.
不会那么久 赌场会计会像老鹰一样盯着
Not that long. Not with casino accountants watching the take like hawks.
有没有可能是坏人将其藏得够久
But could the bad guys hide it in the margins long enough to get away with it
在会计发现之前逃脱惩罚
before the calculator crew catches on?
桑切斯和奥罗斯科 是自由职业赌场保安
Sanchez and Orozco do freelance casino security.
也许事情是从他们开始的
I mean, maybe it all started with them.
他们偶然发现了一件大事 需要帮忙
They stumbled onto something big, they needed help...
所以他们联系了弗朗茨 或许还有斯旺
So they reached out to Franz... maybe Swan.
这件事可能与赌博有关
Guess this whole thing could be tied to gaming.
我是艾莉 为你们服务 你们需要什么
I'm Ellie, I'll be your server. What can I get you?
我们找安全总监
The casino's director of security.
请立刻带我们去吧
Now, please.
你们是110小组的
So, you're the 110th.
是我们组剩下的成员
What's left of us.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科总是提起你们
Sanchez and Orozco talk about you guys all the time.
请坐
Please.
你之前很了解他们吗
So, you knew them well?
是的 他们会对木板人行道 所有赌场进行背景调查
Uh, yeah. They would do background checks for all the casinos on the boardwalk.
等等 你刚说:“之前了解”
Hold on. Uh, you just said "knew them."
过去时
Past tense.
我们认为他们可能已经死了
We have reason to believe they might be dead.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
我上个月在白宫三明治店 吃午餐的时候还见过他们
I-I just saw them, uh, while I was picking up lunch at White House Subs last month.
-我能帮什么忙吗 -这些数据有什么意义吗
How can I help? These numbers mean anything to you?
就这么看没什么意义
Not offhand.
那“六千五 每手十万”呢
What about the phrase, "650 at 100k each"?
不知道 这究竟是怎么回事
No. Uh, what's this all about?
桑切斯和奥罗斯科可能一直在调查
We think Sanchez and Orozco
一起价值六千五百万的赌博骗局
may have been looking into a $65 million gambling scam.
好吧
Okay.
你们说的“六千五”可能是 被操纵的老虎机或固定手牌
Uh, well, in that case, your "650" could be rigged slot machines or fixed hands of poker,
但每手十万 那可是相当高的赌注
but at 100k per hand, that'd be incredibly high stakes.
我现在就可以告诉你们 我们的账都是对的
And I can tell you right now, our books are on mark.
一分钱都不少
All right? We're not missing a penny.
那你的竞争对手呢
What about your competitors?
我可以打听一下
You know, I can... I can ask around,
看是否有人知道桑切斯 和奥罗斯科在调查什么案子
see if anyone knew what Sanchez and Orozco were working on.
-那样可能会缩小范围 -你打听时 也顺道查查这些名字
That might narrow it down for you. While you're at it, run these names,
看是否有人用其中的名字 登记入住酒店
see if any of them are registered at a hotel in town.
这可能要花几个小时 你们住哪儿
Uh... you know, this-this might take a few hours. Where are you guys staying?
我们还不知道
Don't know yet.
那请让我来安排吧
Well, then, please, allow me.
不需要
Not necessary.
那不行 你们可是 桑切斯和奥罗斯科的朋友
No, no. Any friends of Sanchez and Orozco.
看来我们现在只有一间套房了
Well, it looks like all we have available is a suite.
我猜那也够了吧
I guess that'll have to do.
跟我来 我会安排你们安顿下来
Come on, I'll get you guys settled in.
-我们去住汽车旅馆就行了 -雷彻
We'll be fine at a motel. Reacher,
当有人请你免费住套房时 直接答应就好
when someone offers to comp you a suite, just say yes.
我们会让他们送你 一张公园长椅 让你睡觉
Yeah. We'll have them send you up a park bench to sleep on.
你会有宾至如归的感觉
You'll feel right at home.
雷彻 你不会还想住汽车旅馆吧
What was that about a motel, Reacher?
这地方肯定有水疗中心
Whoa. I bet this place has a spa.
我要蒸桑拿
I'm gonna take a schvitz.
这还是个海景房
Ooh. Dibs on the ocean view.
奥唐纳和内格利找到了吧台
O'Donnell and Neagley found the bar.
里面“库存”充足
It's fully stocked.
不过一会就不够了 放好行李了吗
Not for long. You unpacked?
好了
Yup.
我很多年没住过 没标榜“家庭友好”的酒店了
I haven't been in a hotel that wasn't advertised as "family friendly" in years.
我还是不敢相信 大卫奥唐纳有孩子了
I still can't believe David O'Donnell procreated.
还是计划生育
On purpose, anyway.
我记得某人曾吹嘘说 唯一称你为“爸爸”的人
Yeah, I seem to remember someone bragging that the only people that would call you Daddy
是跟你睡过的女人
were the women you slept with.
我现在还跟叫我“爸爸”的人一起睡
I still sleep with people who call me Daddy.
如果外面打雷 我还是跟三个一起睡
Sometimes all three of them if it's thundering outside.
你很快就会知道的 迪克森
You'll find out soon enough, Dixon.
-你怀孕了 -什么
You're pregnant? What?
没有
No. Shit no.
她订婚了 怎么 你不知道
No, she's engaged. What, you didn't know?
终于有人套住了我们的小母马
Someone finally lassoed our little filly.
不
No,
我不知道
I, um, didn't...
关于订婚那事 你们不必留时间过来了
Yeah. Well, about that, you guys can, uh, unsave the date.
好家伙 真的
Fuck. Seriously?
你了解我的 我一直是个数字女孩 一直都有人生计划
Yeah, I mean, you know me. I've always been a numbers gal, always had a life plan.
计划在一定的年龄 某一年结婚
Plan said to get married at a certain age, certain year.
然后 一天 我看到了他手机上的短信
And then one day, I see text messages on his phone.
说:“嘿 亲爱的 等不及周五见面了
It says, "Hey, sweetheart, can't wait to see you Friday.
-“我爱你”等等 -不是吧
I miss you." And all of that.
没人能对迪克森不忠
No. No one steps out on Dixon.
显然他也不行
Not even him, apparently.
短信是他即将来拜访的侄女发的
Text messages were from his niece who was visiting.
但我发现当我以为他出轨时
But I realized that when I thought he was cheating,
我
I was, uh...
我松了一口气
I was relieved.
他是个很正直的人 我
I mean, he's a decent man. I...
如果你要和某人共度一生
I don't know, if you're gonna spend the rest of your life with somebody,
难道你不想感受一些 舒服之外的东西吗
don't you want to feel something more than comfort?
难道你不想觉得刺激
I mean, don't you want to feel excitement,
当你看见他时 有一点震动的感觉吗
a little jolt of something when you see him?
有那么一刻 我以为 我会平静且毫无内疚地摆脱婚姻
Anyways, you know, for a moment I thought I was gonna get out of it with no mess and no guilt,
但相反 我摆脱了婚姻
but instead, I got out of it with...
却非常混乱 满满的负罪感
A lot of mess and a whole lot of guilt.
答对了
Bingo.
这对你来说是好事
Good for you.
卡拉迪克森没有安定下来
Karla Dixon doesn't settle.
谢谢
Thank you.
因此我接了卧底工作
That's actually why I took the undercover job.
花一点时间远离这一切
Take a little time away from it all.
给我解释一下 你怎么会同时当卧底和法务会计的
Explain to me how undercover work and forensic accounting go together?
首席执行官从德州一家公司 侵吞了数百万美元
Well, um, CEO embezzling millions from a company down in Texas,
那里每个人都携带枪支 如果被逼到绝路 他绝对会用武器
where everybody's packing some kind of heat, and he was the kind of guy to use it if cornered,
所以除了数字分析之外 还有一点吸引力
so got a little intrigue along with the number-crunching.
好吧
All right.
你呢 内格利
And what about you, Neagley?
我每次查看领英网 都看到你升职了
Every time I check my LinkedIn, you're getting promoted again.
我过得很好
I'm having fun.
解决了大案子 现在带团队
On big cases, running a team now.
我之前试着 跟一家庞大的软件公司签合同
Trying to land this huge software company as a client.
我成功了 从那份值钱的合同里面收获颇丰
I pull it off, I get a taste of that fat contract.
赚了不少钱啊
Making it rain.
我别无选择 我想给我爸请全天候护理
No choice. I really want to get my dad on round-the-clock nursing care
给他租个离我近的房子 但那需要钱
and rent him a nice place closer to me, but that takes capital.
为什么要租呢 直接买下来
Why rent? Buy and build equity.
不 搞套公寓 合作社就是他妈的香蕉共和国
Get a condo. Co-ops are fucking banana republics.
是啊
Yeah.
你呢 大狗狗 几乎音信全无
What about you, big dog? Being awfully quiet over there.
置业就像养蛇当宠物 或参加交际舞比赛
Home ownership is like keeping snakes as pets or ballroom dancing competitions.
如果你对此感兴趣 那没问题
Fine, if that's what you're into.
-但我不喜欢 -那你觉得稳定的工作有吸引力吗
I just don't see the appeal. Or the appeal of a steady job.
企业界似乎跟军队也没什么区别
Corporate world doesn't seem that different from the Army,
总感觉像是个牢笼
and that always felt a little like a cage.
只是不知道其他的事情
Just didn't know anything else.
我之前在酒吧里 有人演奏《狼嚎》
Then one day I was in a bar, and someone plays Howlin' Wolf
歌唱夜晚路过的火车
singing about trains going by in the night.
那听起来像是真正的自由
That sounded like real freedom to me.
你像博科思卡尔威利一样 跳上货运列车
Are you jumping on freight trains like Boxcar Willie?
有时
Sometimes.
大多数时候 我坐公交车或搭便车
Mostly I take buses or hitchhike.
哪种疯子才会让世界上 块头最大的流浪汉上车啊
What kind of lunatic is picking up the world's biggest drifter?
-他们很有意思 -你在哪里吃饭
They can be interesting. Where do you eat?
我从窗台上偷馅饼
I steal pie off windowsills.
-我说真的 -小饭馆
I'm being serious. Diners.
有时让我搭便车的人 会分享食物 跟我一起吃饭
Sometimes people who pick me up share a meal with me.
-有时是我分享给他们 -你睡哪儿
Sometimes I share with them. Where do you sleep?
大多数时候住在廉价汽车旅馆里
Cheap motels mostly.
如果你找不到汽车旅馆呢
And what if you can't find one?
停泊在码头的无人看管的船只 也很适合住一晚
Unattended boats in marinas are good for a night.
熄火的卡车的平板也适合
Flatbeds of parked trucks.
有一次 我在发现的吊床上 睡了个好觉
Had a great night's sleep in a hammock I spotted in some guy's backyard once
-可惜洒水器浇灭了我的美梦 -天啊
till the sprinklers went off. Good God, man.
-你还真是一根棍和一块布就走天下 -行李太多了
All you need is a stick and a bindle. Too much luggage.
还有问题吗
Any more questions?
有 只有一个
Yeah, just one.
你从来不觉得孤单吗
Don't you ever get lonely?
任您吃自助餐
有人把标语当成个人挑战了呀
Looks like someone took the sign as a personal challenge.
多琳 我只是在热身
Doreen, I'm just warming up.
如果你喜欢晚餐 请务必试一下尼普顿的自助早餐
If you liked the dinner, make sure to try Neptune's breakfast buffet.
每天早上六点开始
Every day, starting at 6:00 a.m.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来我不是唯一一个睡不着的
Looks like I'm not the only one who couldn't sleep.
数字让我放松
Numbers relax me.
如果我要做点数学计算 不如顺便赚点钱 我要叫停
Figured if I was gonna do math, I might as well make some walking-around money. Stand.
你的两只手上显示的是十和八
Ma'am, you're showing ten and eight on two of your hands.
没错 我可以加倍下注 赌上一切换取更大的回报
That's right. And I could double down and risk it all for a potentially larger payout.
或者我也可以叫停 保证能获胜
Or I could stand and have a guaranteed win
因为下一张牌亮牌时 你就输光了
because the next card out of that shoe is gonna bust you.
我祖母曾经说 “不可人心不足蛇吞象”
My grandmother always said, pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered.
她可不是蛇
She's no hog.
我不是蛇 所以我要叫停
I'm no hog, so I'm gonna stand.
如你所愿
As you wish.
十五
15...
太多了
Too many.
恭喜你 女士
Congratulations, ma'am.
你今晚非常幸运
You're having a very lucky night.
我们想请你去听音乐会 庆祝一下
Maybe you'd like to celebrate with a concert on us?
-谢谢 -八十年代的女士们
Thank you. Ladies of the '80s.
黛比吉布森 蒂芙尼和泰勒戴恩 会表演她们最热门的歌曲
Debbie Gibson, Tiffany, and Taylor Dane performing their biggest hits.
你可以赶上下半场
If you hurry, you can actually catch the second half.
但我玩得很开心
But I'm having fun.
我们知道你在算牌
Ma'am, we know you're counting cards.
用脑子算牌是合法的
Which isn't illegal if you do it in your head.
但鉴于你们的安全主管 好心给我们安排了一间套房
But seeing that your chief of security was kind enough to comp us a suite,
我就放你们一马吧
I'll cut you some slack.
动动你的肌肉 把这些筹码送到收银窗口去
Want to use those muscles and help me carry these to the cashier window?
把这些票给穿着会员专用夹克的人
And you can give these tickets to the guy in the Members Only jacket.
他看起来很喜欢八十年代的女士
He looks like he would enjoy some '80s ladies.
谢谢你陪我
Thanks for coming with.
深夜散步总能让我头脑清醒
Late-night walks always clear my head,
我收到内格利发来说弗朗茨死了的 短信后 我的脑子就一直有点乱
and after the text I got from Neagley about Franz, my head's been kind of cloudy, you know?
是啊
Yeah.
我很惊讶你口袋里 装着赌场赚来的那些钱还能散步
I'm surprised you can walk at all with all the casino's money in your pockets.
我猜法务会计会在税款申报的时候 附上这一笔钱吧
Can I assume the forensic accountant's gonna declare that cash on her taxes?
那些骗子
Those crooks?
要是我能审计某人的话 那简直是我梦想的工作
If there's anybody I could audit... Actually, it's kind of my dream job.
现在的工作满足不了你吗
Current gig doesn't give you your auditing fix?
不行 我正在抓一个 从亿万富翁那里偷钱的百万富翁
No, I'm just busting millionaires from stealing from billionaires.
我想做的是追查 政府的腐败和浪费行为
What I really want to do is go after government corruption and waste.
你以前在山姆大叔手下工作过
Oh, you used to work for Uncle Sam.
-六百美元的坐便圈 -没错
You know what I'm talking about. $600 toilet seats. Exactly.
如果税收能被有效使用 我们可以修路和桥梁
I mean, if tax money was spent efficiently, honestly, we could fix roads and bridges
以及学校 我们可以帮助需要帮助的人
and schools. Like, we could help people who actually need help.
我们可以有所作为
We could make a difference.
你应该这么做
You should do it.
是啊
Yeah.
我考虑过自己成立非营利监督组织
Well, I looked into starting my own nonprofit watchdog group,
但启动成本让人望而却步
but start-up costs are prohibitive.
第一步总是最难的
First step's always the hardest.
是的
Yeah.
这就是我们以前 从没有发生过关系的原因吗
Is that why, back in the day, you and I never happened?
第一步是最难的
First steps were the hardest?
你在酒店房间里喝了多少
How much did you drink back at the hotel room?
足够我问你那个问题了
Enough to ask you that question.
快说 我以前给过你提示
I mean, come on, Reacher. It's not like I didn't drop any hints.
当时我是你的老大
I was your boss.
那样做不对
It wouldn't have been right.
我等了好几年才等到这个答案 不愧是你雷彻的作风
Wow. [sighs] Well, I waited years for that answer, and it's pure Reacher.
直接 诚实且有理有据
Direct, honest and well-reasoned.
我能再问你个问题吗
So, can I ask you another question?
你想怎么对付那两个跟踪我们的人
What do you want to do about the two guys that are following us?
-你什么时候发现的 -我们离开赌场时就发现了
When'd you spot them? Ooh, when we left the casino.
我以为他们是看到我们兑的现金 想抢劫我们
Figure they saw us cashing out and now they're gonna try to rob us.
我本来也是这么想的
That's what I thought, too.
看见停在那边
But see that car
-有纽约临时牌照的车了吗 -怎么了
parked up the street with the New York dealer tags? Yeah.
我们进城时 它在高速路上跟着我们
Pretty sure it was behind us on the expressway when we came into town.
我们经过它时 肯定会有个持枪的男人走出来
Also, pretty sure when we walk by it, a man with a gun will step out.
我们转身逃跑时 我们身后的人 不会离得那么远
Then, when we turn to run, the guys behind us won't be so far behind anymore.
计划是什么
So what's the plan?
我们不会经过那辆车
We're not gonna walk by that car.
我说“走” 就翻过栅栏
On my "go," over the fence.
走
Go.
他妈的
Fuck.
走
Go, go.
好的 因为你打了那个警察 肯定会发布你的逮捕令
Okay, there's got to be a warrant out for you in New York for hitting that cop.
如果我们在住宅区开枪 警察就会被叫来 你会被关起来
We open fire in a residential area, cops get called, you get locked up.
我们别用枪
Let's do this without guns.
看起来他们也是这么想的
Looks like they have the same idea.
需要我帮你处理你负责的人吗
Need help with yours?
我能处理
I'll manage.
该死 我们小时候 会把名字写在混凝土里
Damn, Reacher. When we were kids, we just wrote our names in it.
是赌场里穿着会员专用夹克的男人
It's the Members Only jacket guy from the casino.
妈的 如果他们追杀我们 他们可能也会去追杀内格利和奥唐纳
Oh, shit. If they went after us, they might go after Neagley and O'Donnell, too.
不会 他们一直等到我们离开 木板人行道才动手
No, they waited until we were off the boardwalk to make their move.
他们不会去 到处都是监控的繁忙的酒店
They're not gonna go into a busy hotel with cameras everywhere.
没有身份证
No I.D.
我们搜一下这个混蛋的车
Let's search this asshole's car.
看起来有人做了功课
Looks like someone did their homework.
手机
Phone.
成了吗
Is it done?
成是成了 就是跟你想的不一样
Not in the way you expected.
你惹错人了
You're fucking with the wrong guy, Reacher.
你应该知道你不会有好下场的
You should know that this doesn't end well for you.
那为什么是你听起来在瑟瑟发抖
Then why are you the one that sounds scared?
-我觉得我引起他的注意了 -我们要追踪号码吗
Think I got his attention. Should we trace the number?
这是一次性手机 刚才接电话那人也会用一次性手机
This is a burner. Guy on the other end will be using a burner, too.
临时牌照是幽灵车牌 车牌号已经被刮掉了
Dealer tags are most likely ghost plates, VIN's been scratched off.
没什么能指认他们身份的东西
Nothing to I.D. any of them.
这些人都是专业杀手
These guys are pros.
我们应该留个活口的
We should've left one of them alive.
是啊 他们没给我们很多选择
Yeah, but they didn't give us much of a choice, did they?
也许没有 现在我们的线索断了
Maybe not. Now we have nothing to go on.
不一定
Not necessarily.
停车场通行证
Parking lot pass.
-“新时代科技” -对
"New Age Technologies." Yeah.
昨天早上盖的章
Stamped yesterday morning.
这就是你口中的线索
I think it's what you call a clue.
我们怎么处理尸体
Now what are we gonna do about those bodies?
我有个主意
I have an idea.
我口渴了
I'm thirsty.
想喝啤酒吗
Want to get a beer?
新时代有什么发现吗
Anything on New Age?
有
Yeah,
看起来新时代是一家航空航天公司
looks like New Age is an aerospace company.
跟大西洋城有联系吗
Any ties to Atlantic City?
我看没有 它的总部设在纽约
Not that I can see. Headquarters are based in New York.
有一块弹片打中我了 刚才太过刺激 我没注意
Looks like a piece of shrapnel bit me. I didn't notice with all the adrenaline pumping.
几乎没伤到你
Barely winged you.
这里
Here.
你在干什么
What you doing?
给伤口抹酒精很疼 我妈以前就这么做
What my mom used to do when the alcohol stung.
你可能只把细菌吹进去了
You know, you're probably just blowing germs into it.
可能吧 但感觉很好
Probably. But it feels good.
谢谢
Thanks.
不用谢
Welcome.
你知道 雷彻
You know, Reacher,
有时感觉孤单是很正常的
it's perfectly normal to be lonely sometimes.
任何人像你这么过日子都会孤单
Anyone living their life the way you do would.
今晚你不必孤单
But you don't have to be lonely tonight.
而且你也不再是我的老大了
And you're not my boss anymore.
科罗拉多州丹佛市外32公里处
所有六千五百万都将装在卡车里
All 650 will be in the truck.
你可以用我在车上 装的GPS定位器追踪
You can track the shipment with the GPS locater I paired to this.
路上至少标记了两个好的伏击点
There are at least two good ambush points marked on the route.
很好
Excellent.
我的人会处理剩下的事
My men will take care of the rest.
那武器呢
And the weapons?
都会在海外使用吗 这是说好了的
They'll all be used overseas? I was told that was the deal.
那当然
Absolutely.
卡车司机不会受到伤害吧
And the, and the truck driver won't be harmed?
当然
Of course.
我永远不会伤害任何人
I would never harm anyone.
-早上好 迪克森 -我们需要谈谈昨晚的事
Morning, Dixon. We need to talk to you about what happened last night.
整个酒店都听到昨天的动静了
Oh, the whole hotel heard what happened last night.
我就说你声音很大
Told you you were loud.
这是昨天在从纽约就开始 跟踪我们的车里找到的
Found this in a car that followed us down from New York yesterday.
司机怎么了
What happened to the driver?
他不会跟我们回去
He won't be following us back.
他的那两个朋友也不会
Neither will his two friends.
妈的
Shit.
-是谁 -赖特
Who is it? Wright.
安全
Clear.
进来
Come on in.
你们看起来有点紧张啊
You, uh, you folks seem a little jumpy.
鉴于目前的情况 我不能怪你们
I mean, I don't blame you, given the circumstances.
我很讨厌传达更多坏消息 但我调查这些事情时
And I hate to be the bearer of more bad news, but when I was looking into things,
大西洋城警察局跟我说 他们在纽约北部发现了两具尸体
Atlantic City PD told me that two more bodies have been discovered in Upstate New York,
就在他们发现你们朋友的地方附近
near where they found your other friend.
从分解情况来看 他们已经在那儿有段时间了
Judging by the decomposition, they'd been there a while.
我拿到了一份警察报告副本
Got a copy of the police report for you.
很容易借此识别其身份
Pretty easy to I.D. him with that.
他参军时 他姐姐很害怕
When he joined the Army, his sister was terrified
他会伤痕累累地死去
he'd be killed with some disfiguring wounds.
她永远不会知道发生了什么
She'd never know what happened to him.
就说他的兵牌可能被炸掉
Said his dog tags could be blown off.
为了安抚她 他在后背上 文了他的名字和服役编号
To calm her down, he got his name and service number tattooed across his back.
看起来很可笑
Looked ridiculous.
他不在乎
He didn't care.
他爱他的姐姐
He loved his sister.
我得给她打电话
I'm gonna have to call her.
我会告诉米莱娜豪尔赫的遭遇
I'll tell Milena about Jorge.
他们的伤口跟弗朗茨的吻合
Their wounds match Franzy's.
这意味着他受到了折磨 然后被扔下了直升机
Meaning he was tortured and tossed out of a helicopter.
还有一件事
Uh, one other thing.
没有人用你给我的名字 登记入住任何酒店
Um, no one using any of the names you gave me have checked into any of the hotels in town.
我跟其他赌场的同行谈过了
And I talked to my counterparts at the other casinos.
奥罗斯科和桑切斯 没有替他们查任何案子
Orozco and Sanchez, they weren't working on anything for any of them.
我跟他们说六千五百万的赌博骗局时
And when I told them about the $65 million gambling scam,
他们连夜查账 我也是
they pulled their overnight audits. I did, too.
一切都在可接受的损失幅度中
Everything is within acceptable loss margins.
没有人以任何一家赌场为目标
No one has hit any of the casinos.
你不必担心
You don't have anything to worry about.
尸体都是在纽约发现的 跟踪我们的车是从纽约来的
Bodies were found in New York, car that followed us was from New York.
是纽约的幽灵车牌和停车证件
New York ghost tags, New York parking pass.
这一直是纽约的案子
This has always been a New York case.
你要去哪里
Where the hell are you going?
我们需要更多的枪
We're gonna need more guns.